Deliver us from evil.
The Carpenter's Son is a horror film directed by Lotfy Nathan.
A remote village in Roman-era Egypt explodes into spiritual warfare when a
carpenter, his wife and their child are targeted by supernatural forces.
The Carpenter, played by Nicolas Cage.
The Boy, played by Noah Jupe.
The Mother, played by FKA twigs.
The Stranger, played by Isla Johnston.
Lilith, played by Souheila Yacoub.
Leper Woman, played by Kaiti Manolidaki.
The Carpenter's Son is a 2025 supernatural thriller film written and directed by Lotfy Nathan
and starring actors Nicolas Cage, FKA Twigs, Noah Jupe and Souheila Yacoub.
The film is inspired by the Infancy Gospel of Thomas.
The film was first released in Argentina on October 30, 2025, and then
was released in the United States on November 14, 2025.
The film explores themes of faith, greece, crete, carpenter, temptation.
The tone is dark.